Voices collide, the storm and the flame
Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive
In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive
Who's awake? We're awake
Who's afraid? Let it break
From shadows to starlight, the truth will be shown
The Psyche awakens, you're never...
The Unexpected.
psyche's show
I shouldn't have thought out
A part of my brain was fried
I thought that I could win but the chat just sighed
Won't you banish me?
They said I wasn't reasonable
Nothing was to blame
I mean, it's like, it's a different show.
And I loved being in our show once again.
Do you like the, do you like that?
Is it gonna be Hollywood here?
I don't know.
You like the song?
Thank you.
It's actually based on an Elisa Jordana song
called Taxi to the Dark Side of the City,
or Dark Side of the City.
But, and so I just kind of changed it around a little bit
Well not a parody of that song, but it's kind of like just adapted for the
Halibur's. You might like, you're not like this video though, Hammer. I think I have one more video to show you.
I have to share my screen.
I don't know if you guys have all seen this one, but it's pretty good.
And the night turns long
When the leaves turn red
She rises in shadows
And strong
Lilith in Scorpio, my anima flame
Whispers my secrets calls out my name
Like it everyone leave. Oh
No, I'm saying I don't know. I guess like everyone was like
Hey, loser. I don't know. I don't know. Maybe not. I don't know
Guess that is more interesting people in me, huh?
hollywood right here i some more stuff to show you
she's on the trip to that is me
so yeah i was on trip to class
Ready to see it? Oh, I don't know how much we'll watch a bit. I don't know, it's just like, it's my own show on it so I'm sure I can play it, but I'm stuck on this one.
There you go, okay. Um, okay, so let's see. This one.
Then add a share screen.
It's off.
Which direction we are going?
There's no knowing where we're going
Or which way the river's flowing
Is it raining?
Is it snowing?
Is a hurricane of blowing?
Not a speck of light is showing, so the danger must be growing.
Are the fires of hell a-clawing?
Is the grizzly reaper mowing?
Yes!
The danger must be growing for the rowers to keep on rowing!
And they're certainly not showing any signs that-
He must be still in love with this guy because it's like you can't of him is Carl. He's like Carl
Carl, but anyway, so Carl like
Was mad or something last night and she's like insight was like he's fault. I don't know. How was my fault or anything?
She's like, but he hates psyche. He's like, oh, okay. I'm saying, okay. Oh, yeah. Well, you know
No, no, I like him now. No, he's smart. He's a smart guy. And so
And she's like, oh this thing is like, you know psyche like a little
He's such a bottom-feeder. And you know, I fail to see that right now, but she will, you know,
thank you this and that. I'm a bottom-feeder. And she's like, and you know, he goes when he's not
wanted. He's not wanted here. He's not wanted at Emma's. I was like, okay. She always is saying,
oh, come to my chat. And you know, it's not coming to yours. I was, you know, even if everyone's
I said, oh, thanks for just letting me know no one wanted me there like finally, you know, because you're always telling me like I want you there
anyway, so
And then they did attack me in the chat and so I'm unmodded and
I have to unmod her again eventually. I'm just a little bit lazy to do it, but
I don't even care. What's going on? I don't know
dealing with a nut. Scorpio. And Bita was like, oh, he's making songs about me. Yeah,
I did make a couple songs, like probably three songs, but the pictures I was
putting up, like, I made one song I'm playing about her, right? But the other
songs are about Lilith and Scorpio, right?
And then he's like, you know what, this friendship is over.
I'm like, oh, fine.
Jeez, fine.
I mean, I've been trying to give it mouth-to-mouth
resistance teaching in CPR for months.
It's like, I'm just like, I'm going to lose this.
So what have I said about her?
Like, really nothing bad.
I mean, maybe today I have, but it's like, you know.
Hey, what did she say about me?
Whipster, scammer, everyone in the chat yelling me.
Let everyone in the chat, like, oh, I'm a terrible person,
right?
I love join your panel psyche and I just try to join beat us, but like she's not even there like oh beat
Is taking a big shit
Like if you're going to be a professional like psyche right here. He's a professional. He's always on top of his job
Be the I don't I'm not here to cuss out beta, but you've got to be more professional beta
You've got you're being very unprofessional baby beta and we're not up here for it
Your defense, she can go to the bathroom and she doesn't have to be there to pick up the pick up
Yeah, but she was gone for like 20 minutes
Like if you got to use the bathroom don't go live if you're gonna be gone for 20 minutes
You got to shit your brains out. Go do what you got to do
Sometimes I have to go when you gotta go you gotta go. What up Van Gogh?
That's my boy Van Gogh right there man. That's like a brother to me Van Gogh. It's like a fucking brother to me man
Hello, Joey. You have it?
What up, man? Can you repeat that in English? You fucking you British bastard?
Mate, I'm not fucking English. Oh, yeah, you're fucking Scottish Viking mate. Get it?
I don't give a fuck what you are. I will you with my fist
Yeah, I was what be the finish shitting and I'll go attack be the let's all go to be different color day
So now I got be this guy's like people after me now like, you know, Joe just came here try to
Messes me and then like the peep-peep person just put up some like you know some
Photoshopped staying with my face on it like you know me like smoking and the cats are in the room
I mean, it's like oh
Like not a litter box inside. Oh, yeah, we were so funny
He probably uses a litter box instead of a toilet. That's why they're we're going to litter boxes
But actually like I'm very well-trained actually do not go to the bathroom the house. I don't know what's so weird about that
Apparently I'm
Little bit weird. I must be high as a kite. I wish I mean I wish what's the kite called? Well, I'll brew
Oh, it'll be as big as a complain is that I'm playing clips for my own show. I mean, it's like
Can I fucking run my own show? I mean, I don't understand. Why are you having this get stuck?
Why are you hiding this for it's like hello? Do I tell you how to run your show at one time?
I know believe someone's comment that I was basically like I'm you know an axe murderer
kittens and you know and you got mad at me. I mean it's like so yeah I don't know
what's going on lately it's just like all these like
People say I was crazy shit. I don't know if you're hearing what they're saying. It's like it doesn't make any sense to me
You know what?
Tell me what you're hearing and I'll tell you what I'm hearing because I think we might have you know, there might be a confusion
hearing like
Let's go play the Bizkit song on Psyche's channel another thousand times and like harass him with that word.
Yesterday, I apologized to Bita too. You know, I'll just, I'm just gonna say I apologized to her. You know, I don't want to fight anymore.
I don't want the fighting anymore. I want you guys to be friends. You know, I don't want no drama anymore. You know, I killed her.
I can, I can be perfectly fine for like two hours on the phone and like be like perfect
And then it's like as soon as she goes on the air and like it's like a different person
It's like and it's I can't like do that cognitive dissonance with people anymore
It's like I can't like have them good relationship with them privately and like publicly they're like, you know
She said I'm a bottom-feeder today. She said I was like not welcome on her show and all this kind of stuff that she never said before so
Was that what you was live?
Oh, wow
Bro, that's but see I was trying to be good. I apologize to her. I want you guys to be right
No, like you is it's like it's like me it's like I think she'll look even like I don't think she's mad at me because of you
It's just one of like like a million reasons. Yeah, but I'm gonna see I'm trying to do everything on my end
You know to try to help out your guys is you know
And really nothing will help except like, you know, it's just getting along like
I mean, it's like I'll try to get along with her, but it's like she keeps letting people like really like go
Like oh, yeah, someone said horrible things about her and stuff like that
She's still talking to them and like, you know, she's still going back and forth and
Well, yeah, look at black RG man. He docks her and she still you know has them as a mod like like go figure talk about oxymoron, right?
like
That's actually just caught so
Thank you
Yeah
Hi Jesus Christ. Come on up. Anyone else want to join? You're welcome up.
God, I just want to plug my own book.
I will
Have it so it's ever set up right now. It's only on sale one place right now
I'm gonna try to get it on Amazon print. I'm gonna try to get a print version of it
Yeah, I will get print for you print on the man for sure
But it's not like a huge thing. It's not a very very long book
So that will take a little while to get that format, right? So, um
But I will also, you know, I'll be I'll be
There's no AI right now like you're talking about but I'm allowed to play my songs that I made and people understand
It's like these things like the AI is just spinning out everything. It's like, you know, it's like
Being very heavily programmed. Thank you so much. I want to show you a little bit of the book, too. It's really cool
so
That's the Trollopedia
I read a lot of it today, but you can see this is a really cool game.
Nobody cares about you, Mr. Damien.
Let me get my...let me get this out for a minute.
Let's see.
I'm about to have a little cleanup in the chat.
Can I up on aisle 3?
Can I up on aisle 3, please?
Can we get these just haters out of here?
Haters, why don't you go do something people in the chat that haven't problem me? Hey, Jay dog. Yo, what's going on psyche?
Yo, yo, yo
Hey, man, what's what are all these people talking about? They're all fucking talking bullshit, man
Yeah, they just need to get a life. I mean there's having no life so they have to try to like look in mind
Oh, you don't know you could down do these motherfuckers there
You know, they're told bro, and they're trying to say you choose Jay dog over beat up bro. You choose
True you choose yourself your own piece of mind you choose
You know you're your own person. You're not gonna be bullied by beta
No one asked for your opinion diamante and by an AMC reborn by you're not welcome here. Bye
MC hidden
It's just people trying to like say any like little thing I can say it's like do you know like people use like actually like
Most celebrities that don't have a ghost writer and things like that. So it's like not even
So yeah, I know who's talking shit
But yeah, I mean, yeah, obviously my you know, uh
Let's see. Oh tyron big um, yeah, he's back. It's just it's a this is you know, this is amc
beat it big time or time like I think it is bull I think what she's doing is
bullying you know like I think because it's like I didn't think but whatever
this was we talked about this was before like I talked to Alexander and
Alexander like mediated like that's not talking about each other and that's
fine and I was like we'll do that but then today like the whole day I was just
mentioned on the show in a really bad way
And it was like, it was noticed by more than just me,
like, and, you know, it's kind of like, really like,
I mean, it's a disagreement, it's turning into like something else
because it's like, she won't let it go.
She won't even let it, like, but Arthur said to her like,
I think four or five months ago. I mean, I think this is just she'll still bring that up every time like the first thing
Well, you didn't did them it's like it's like the same argument and it's getting really tiresome like having the same argument
it's like I
Mean it's like I would choose her but it's like she won't let me apologize
She won't let me do she won't let me on her show without being like having everyone attack me
She won't stop slandering me. I mean, it's like so I can only take so much, you know, I love her but it's like I wasn't
And they can't say she's not bullying you. What is bullying like if we look up the definition and the webster's dictionary
Bullying is doing something and trying to make somebody do something
Against their will and make them do stuff like, you know, that's bullying
Bullying can be also like pushing people over the edge
Yeah
Yeah, when I unalive themself or something like that, I think that's like really scary kind of bullying it's like
Whatever they're whatever their reason for is it's like that's not a friend that would like try to do that to you, right?
Yeah, yeah, exactly man. That's why I'm playing some of the old stuff back because it's like there's a lot of stuff I missed
She's ranging me for hours. Yeah, I know she I mean I went over there
I was like why is she still mad like I just because of this video and it's like why cuz I look I mean
I mean, you know what you know that video speaks truth man
That video is 100% truth on beta thousand percent and you know why a lot of more people are seeing it
You know a lot of people, you know, I'm not gonna say names, but a lot of people in the chat are seeing you know
The truth the way she really is with you the way she get try to bully you
Who in the hell is she to try to tell you who you can have at your mod who you can have in your chat on your panel?
I don't I can't tell her anything by anything. I can't exactly. I was
It would be different if you could you know it would be vice versa if you guys were friends like that and say hey
You can you know help me on my channel and we vice versa
You know if you can go over there and get the same to her then she could do the same for you
You know that would be you know
Kind of like a teeter-totter effect, but it's not it's very one-sided
She just wants to do control your channel and do whatever you want to do on her channel
Because she's been she's streamed like a couple months longer than I did but I also like I had over a thousand subscribers when I met her and stuff
So it's always like I like she made me and stuff like that and I was nothing make you shouldn't make you
Yeah, I mean it's just like
You already would like it like you said you already had a what a thousand plus subscribers before
Before you even knew her like you already were successful before you already knew what you were
I was and it's already in the same communities too like that's why
You already knew at least you already knew you know all the people you already knew yeah, I
Mean I like so so let's see
Yeah, okay, so man, I see all these porn bombers and stuff like that
Yeah, enjoy the bags of okay, whatever they said, but the I need to turn my all messages
Okay mods you need to turn on all messages and like help me out mods because I just want this it's the same
It's just amc. I need him mom. I need him out of here. Okay
Let's see my day. Oh, those days. Okay, so let me see this person is gone and
That's the only person
No, but yeah
Thank you for getting these people too guys because some of these people are just
really stupid and
He's really really pissed about that video like yeah, I didn't know how much of one trip kick video can ignite
The hate inside somebody could just get drunk and plastered and you know on pills and just fucking
Just go banana apeshit on a panel and just rage about people really really if you think about it
She's been raging and saying our name. She's been saying psyche
And j-dog. She's been saying your name more like because you know this between you and her
But she's been saying it for like the last month and a half if you would go back to like all of her screens on rumble
All of them start with psyche said this or j-dog said this or this and this what happened and
They're making AI videos and songs and pictures and you know this person's hanging out with this one
This one's modded over here. I can't believe you have this like it's all psyche psyche psyche like
Yeah, but she says she don't want to you know, she's not talking about you, right?
But every video if you go back, right?
She keeps on killing message, you know
Bring up your name. Who's here?
Black RG. Hey
Here comes this mother fucker. I don't know RG. RG. I
Can't get so much trash about me RG. Why are you doing that? And then why are you?
I'm gonna do an interview with Emma because it's gonna be that's good. I want you to dog you led Jay dog
Well me raping my dog, so I'm gonna get a lot of
She needs to see him
Okay, well hi, RG. You'll enjoy a mini Emma and stuff like that, but I don't want to have you on I'm saying that
I should see him threatening you like why he came on here and you're just directly just to try to
Cagonize you on behalf of beta
That's that's that's what I hear when he says about me and beat as I thought I was a question
You know, he's like talking total trash about me and it's like I didn't do it in the black Archie ever is exactly
It's all because I
Dog or I know he's saying I let J dogs say something and they do it because you know
I had I had said that in another I had said it in Sandman's chat. It wasn't
Nothing to do with you psyche it wasn't another time. It wasn't on your your chat. It wasn't even on your channel
Okay, well, you know that's a voice changer he's using right? That's a voice changer
No, you know who he sounds like you ever see the movie clerks
No, no, not Jay the
Randall if you go and watch the movie clerks like he sounds just like Randall Graves one of the acts that he's like a comedian
Probably is the same person. It might be in real names Jeff Ang well, I'm not gonna never mind not gonna dots
But he's a famous comedian you look up person clerks Randall Graves, which is a fictional character
That's who he plays in movies
Sounds just like RG and I know he's a voice changer because you know you can pick famous celebrity
You know to mimic their voices and pick it up
And he picked that one because you know, he's kind of the same
You know RG Randall Graves the same thing Randall Graves RG
Sounds exactly the same exactly the same and the characters kind of like a smart ass he kind of characters
You know exactly like what RG is like here
But in the movie
Well, you know, he can go at himself and so yeah
They say I mean I say I mean I'm in the panel bars. I'm not involved in this big drama anymore
Alexander's leaving the
Drama behind some I it's like really I had enough of like
disease different
Dumb west side story
West side story has cooler gangs in this fucking panel verse. I mean it's like I'm just it's like just there's embarrassing and rather much better
Be not affiliated with any of them and just be on my own rather than there's
Ridiculous, yeah, you didn't have to pick a side
You should just be able to be your own person. Yeah, I'm a person. I don't care anymore. It's like
loyalty that's no one that person was not loyal to me
What will you do that person? You know, it's like I
Bro, you look you were so loyal you got branded legit branded
Yeah, that's what you know, that's what that was what you ever see the show Yellowstone
I mean, but yeah, whatever whatever it is. It's like it's a there's a I have a picture of peacock
Like with a peacock has a wound on his chest and it's a wound. That's what it's like to miss the wound
But it's also my cap, so it's like oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah
You just change the lettering a little bit or I can just like say Burger King gang or something
Yeah, bro, bro, but I would give you just change a lettering. Are you know just put it just see what I can do to cover up
Like make little like make little uh
I'll make a design hours out of it or something like that. I don't know. Yeah, or are you know what make it like something like uh
Oh, you know, um
I'll be a big aphor a wig that now put
For la Nord
Well, uh, are you a scorpio psych?
I'm Lilith and Scorpio and then right now it feels like she's like coming out of me
Like it's like a right around like like when right around like September and October like I get like start getting all these
all these that visions of like
the Queen of Hell and stuff like that so
But in a good way in a good way, so I do have Lilith and Scorpio it is one of like the
Psyche is leaving me no no choice with this MS dub. It turns out we have a mutual figure. It's easy. Okay, RG
Anyway, I don't care about Emma anymore. Emma is the old news for me. Okay?
She's nothing compared to Alexandra
exactly
Well, yeah, that was a good show to look at I was catching it off and on you know
I was going in and out, you know, you guys Alex a show kid. I was in the middle of doing something and
Fucking that was a good show man. You guys are talking about the atlas and talking about, you know
It's everything in general and is that really gonna be her last last episode like
How are you talking about? Yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, I was Andrew. Yeah. Um, she's she's like leaving like the
Superverse so my and so yeah, whatever. It's like and
Emma I have not subscribed to her. I have no channels and it's actually I do have some channels
I could I found that I could go on
But I'm not gonna bother her. It's just like I don't have a desire anymore. I'm over it
I got it all out in my in the songs about her and stuff like that all that all that out
So yeah, we'll have fun. She needs more interviews, you know, good. You know get her out there, but I don't know
I don't know if she knows what she's in for but
I saw the threat you made to her in the phone tonight on my phone, so I know you're oh
Yes, definitely send them to them bro. Send that to them
What's that? Yeah, send send the cameras that whatever tracks they made let let go. Yeah, what these guys are up to?
Yeah, I mean
Unfortunate you won't listen to me if anybody else can get to the message and you can't say my name who did that
I'm sure was probably a black RG. I think yeah, because now he's bringing her up again
So
They're all the same thing. They're all like, you know, this little group. It's the AMC and
Well, yeah, they call him the grease game. That's what they call them. It's black RG art Vandal a the Krog
Who else AMC?
Fit sage there
He black RG she said she wants me to not interfere so I won't interfere. Okay. I think she'll see right through though
Hey Mason
Hey, psych are we still cool man?
Yeah, are you mad at me? No, I'm just wondering what's going on. Oh, yeah, we're cool always, okay?
Yeah, yeah
Do you still talk about you're on spunkies a little bit like a week ago. You like spunky
Who's that? She's up. She's like a blonde lady and she's like real nice
Uh, can you show me who you're talking about? I don't know who that is. Yeah, I have a picture. Hold on lies
I was not friends with AMC. I can't I can't scan that guy. That's Tony the conductor. He's a piece of shit
Well, I know you might have been like involved in like him at one point
But hopefully no no no the only way I'm involved with what AMC is because of groovy Jimmy's like that over there in that sector
It's because I crossed paths with him over there. That's the only way I'm involved with that
What's what's her name sponky and what sponky I
Think I think I've talked to her before. Yeah, you were on her show last week and they were like
They're being kind of nice to you. I don't know. I don't I hope like people are nice to you
Like, you know, you're very innocent. It seems like you're very like, you know
I'm not trying to hurt anybody and like it's like worse. It's like it's like where's that goddess named a thing or something a thing that comes or whatever it's
That is the thing that is yeah, I mean, I haven't seen tonight, but he's usually here
Like he's here here
He came the other night. He bought like a bunch of memberships last night. I don't know if you know one
But yeah, he bought like five memberships
So like you're still trying to hook up. Yeah, if you're interested if not, then I understand I don't want to like
You down
I'm still trying to figure this stuff out man with like, you know, I
Still got to figure out figure this out. Yeah, and I think Chris K's kind of figured out
You seen the show last night with Chris K. He like he said
He said he's gonna come over to my house with a hundred thousand dollars and
Then we're gonna do chatterbait together
Sikes worse betas though. I thought you used to talk to betas like the first time we met is the
Yeah, I thought her name was Sarah, but it turns out she lied to me. She's this woman named Dita the whole time and
She wasn't
So you ever go to her stream it like where we were before like when we used to. Yeah, I go there
I was at her stream today, and I was just like hiding in the hiding the features and like
Watching like the head cheerleader, you know, I
Didn't see you though. I mean, I didn't go to it though. I should have went to it, right? Yeah, she's still on the air
I think she might be still be on the air right now
Can you check man? Yeah
I got you let me see I can check um she is yes she's on the air still what do you mean
she's live or what do you mean yeah you can go over there uh can you can you can you
give me the thing to go to I mean can you go over there too well I'm doing my show
right now but I'll give you join her the link to her show yeah but can you meet me over
Yeah, well, I can but it's like I don't think she wants to talk to me and like stuff like that
I don't think she's like she's a really mad at me right now. And so I don't
Why she mad at you? What did you do? What did you do to make her mad?
I do anything. I she thinks I like made fun of her and like was teasing her or like with
I should think I wrote this like a biscuit song that said
She broke her teeth on a biscuit and I doesn't even say that line in it
I don't even think it says her biscuits are dry, but people think it says that you know, yeah, and
Yeah, I don't know
And then she said I was like putting a picture of a witch up. It's not like a witch
It's like it's like it's just lilies and scorpion. It's obviously not her
And you have a picture of like yeah, it's like so what so that's all stuff that went wrong or what?
Yeah, like all that went wrong. It was just I mean it was because like months ago
Some somebody said like oh something about you know that she didn't like and then I didn't say anything really
But I actually did and then she's like
You never defended me. You never and she's like been mad about me ever since we've just been like getting along like a little bit
For like a couple hours and then I thought y'all were friends like
We probably are but it's like
You know friends fight sometimes and I don't but I don't know. I think she's like I don't know if she really likes me at all
I just don't know if she hates me that's the whole thing. It's like
Sikes are you gonna?
Are you gonna be able to go like talk to her again?
Yeah
Can go if I want like but I kind of like me like uh, you know, I was like I'm just gonna stay away and like not not uh
No
You know bother what is the way
What is the way to actually get on there though? Like what do you do?
Oh, this you have to go on the stream yard is like you get on here
You have to go to a stream yard link that she has posted. Can you show me? Yeah, I can get you the link
I didn't know like
Okay, she has SIG on the show right now. Let me see if I can find her link
Okay, now she doesn't have her link up. It's not a whole thing. She does one
Okay
So Mason, this is a spring slide here. Do you know how to go back to the private chat or no?
Do you want to get this in a private chat or the regular chat? Oh
Which one would be better?
Well, I mean it's like because yeah, you know, it's been the private chat. So it's because I only you need it
So there you go. You want to go to betas from here? There you go. Just click that
Say it's like a magical ago. Yeah
Yeah, that's where you go and I'm a kiss before you go though. Yeah
Yeah, you're a kiss the guy
like still there yeah amazing um have you ever kissed a guy
i um i don't remember when i did if i i don't i can't remember man
you remember i thought i remember something like that
no psych i don't think i've ever done it that's why i can't remember
okay well that makes sense well how about how about if you come out here i'll
give you something you remember forget
Oh, goodness gracious.
Like, RG, you know, I'm not dumb, and I know I'm not dumb.
I don't think, but I don't think, you know, I think everyone has some level of intelligence and some kind of beautiful...
Part of their brain that is like nobody else has or something like that. So there's unique people and it's like I don't
Not against people. I'm not gonna attack people. I'm not gonna send manure to people's house or spoiled milk or
You know unpaid dinner orders or you know, call people and mess with their phone lines and stuff like that
And just like just try to make their life hell and make them get worried and stuff like that
I'm not a kind of person that does that
Yeah, I want to get my flirt on, but nobody wants to hit on me.
The only person I did was Chris K, and it's like, I don't know, I don't know if he's
going to come here with the $100,000.
If he does, I don't think I'm going to, I don't know, I wonder what will happen.
Okay, let me see if I have something to watch with my counts unfollowing.
Okay.
Where's your counts unfollowing?
Where in the fuck is it? Where in my channels I'm following?
Oh here. Look, this is like, this is what happened, this is like months ago. This is
like three months ago. I love it. This was three months ago. So since this was three
and even reverse type 2. After all, the real cause of the disease has
Well then you'd better start swimming or you'll sink like a stone for the time they are changed.
Station we had was about you and like Yasin and LD15 and I said you keep doing exactly
what I fucking tell you not to do over and over I'm not crying you guys I'm not I'm
just lost my brain.
Okay no it sounds like she I'm not trying to be mean I'm just saying she's talking about
to cry then.
Michael you're the one that needs to cry okay I'm not crying.
In like that sarcastic with me. I lost my voice because you know
Damn
That's another thing is like you're all right Michael. Just shut up. Nobody even gives a fuck about your input
Okay, with all the respect the only person that really cares
Please Michael
Thank you Casey
When I left a few days ago, you keep saying beta come back beta. I love you beta this and that I say I love you too
I'm not coming back to the channel because I don't want to bring all that shit in here. I don't want to bring the drama
I don't want to bring all of that and I left I was like, you know behind the scenes
I did give you advice and then you did it again over and over and again
I'm like psyche be careful and I did I was fine. I'll take you know what you're not fucking listening
Yeah, I'm not gonna sit there and like, listen,
what were you saying when I hung up?
Are you so self-aware to realize that, you know what?
What I'm trying to tell you is best for you?
No, don't fucking bring my name up, I'm bringing into this.
The way you treated me in summer last night was shit.
You literally put us, you're like, all right, go then, bye.
Get the fuck out, you too.
And yeah, you did call me a lot of fucking names.
You also said you hated me.
You looked at me and you're like, guess what, Bea?
Guess what?
What did you say? I'm the fucking evil person and you're my fool. And then you fucking kicked me like a dog. Yes, I was being sarcastic.
Oh, you're being sarcastic? Did you not message me like in the early mornings with a bunch of messages, Bida, Bida, let's say it was a script.
How am I gonna script summer? How do you want me to cover this shit up for you, psyche?
Yeah, we're not covering shit up no more. That ship has fucking sailed.
Well, sometimes we have had a script sometimes there has been a script
I'm a real person and I have real fucking issues and I'm really fucked up in the head
So I'm really crazy. So guess what? I don't do fucking scripts, but I don't do behind-the-scenes shit. It was even doing it's ridiculous
Thank you psyche. Can I ask you a question? What is your channel about? I've got a basic idea of myself what I believe it's about but
It's about his ego at this point. It's about, you know, how many people are viewing, how much money is coming in.
He doesn't care about who was there from the beginning or end or equal.
Just, you know, every single one of us has put things out there.
I have nothing against DJ Electra. I think she's amazing.
But last night you literally said, DJ Electra, you're the only person that was there for me.
I said in the situation with the
Ann, you also said, I hate you, Bita.
I did not.
Is that how you did?
You called me an in-word.
I did not.
You called her a stand-in-word.
Yes, you did.
I did not.
I don't use that language.
Yes, you do.
When you're drunk.
Give me a clip.
Somebody clip it.
Find that I want to find that. I don't that's not my vocabulary
Yeah
It's like she wouldn't she wouldn't get back to me
And I kept waiting I just waited backstage, but she never said that I was on there
She never put me on there
She like I'm talking or is she not there because I mean she's not there
No, she was no she was talking but she just kept me just waiting and I didn't know what
I think there's a lot of people on our show
I think there's like six people on our panel probably so she this is like
No, there's only one other person on there and I saw it. There's a little I only saw one person
She was talking to she's ignoring you. I don't know why
No, she wasn't ignore me. It's just I don't think she knew I was waiting for her, right? Like the dude
You can see if we're waiting backstage you can see them
Yeah, but I was actually backstage for a long time and she never you know answered to me. Was she ignore me?
Yeah, I think so
It's like how can you figure this out though, man? Like are you gonna try to see how you can figure it out?
Well, I mean it's like I really I mean it's like up to you to figure it out
But I don't have you been on our show before you were on a show before maybe she just like
We did come back to our show recently or something that had a bad appearance or no
The last time I've ever talked to her was the time that I talked to you and you're playing like remember the first time I ever
Met you I think and it was like you're playing on that metal like drum thing
Yeah, it's like these rubber like you know cool things like yeah these metal sticks up thick or something you're playing on it
Yeah
Well, yeah, I have I have a drum and but yeah, I'm sorry. She didn't like you want to see I don't think she's big
She's very happy with me. So I don't know
Psycho what does that have to do with me though? I don't know why she had me waiting for so long
I don't know. I don't know. I think she just like she
Maybe she just like wants to talk to the one person and it's not a topic
Maybe she doesn't like you I don't know but I like you it can't be no
So I can't because she doesn't like me cuz I only been on her stream like one other time
That was with you. This is only time I've been on
I don't know I don't know
Sometimes she has sometimes she just like has like different
You know, I don't know who she wants on her show right now
I don't know I'm not sure but you know you're a nice person
I see and I wish you would have picked up for you, but
You know, I will always pick up for you though. Okay, so yeah
You said I did I ever kiss a guy before?
Yeah, have you?
I don't think I've ever done that though because I don't remember ever doing that. No, well, if you kiss me you would never forget it, right I
Would think so. Yeah
So, uh, you ever want to come back to Los Angeles, you know, like it's like where's it where's that metal things like where's that metal thing that you had the
Drone like drop thing with the metal sticks like that you played is
When you get it yeah, can you get it?
Mason likes the drums guys. I want to check it out, so
We go
So you have like
Can you play something yeah
But it goes by numbers, and I don't know what numbers to do
Name some numbers one through one through one through seven. No, you don't play a basic like
Do you know to play like a basic rock beat or something like that?
They say
Yes
You know that I played a drums too, right? I actually had a drum set and stuff. I played all
Yeah, do you have it? Do you still have one or no?
I used to have one but not any more
Do you look do you look pretty sexy on the drums when you're like you do without your shirt and stuff?
I would think so. Yeah
Like pretty hot. I want to see you drum. Can you send me a video of you drumming without your shirt?
I don't know how I was there a way to send it to you. Yeah, you can just
You know bring it to my house on the video because that
How would I show you though? What do you want me to do?
You just send me a clip on the on the internet. You can just videotape it and then like I'll give my email address
Okay, okay, I'll put my email in the back chat. Yeah
Okay
It's like you played a video games stuff. Yeah, I do. I mean I have GTA. Do you like GTA?
Yeah, what do you play like mainly? That's not what you mainly play
Well, I have a VR set now and so I do different stuff
and I
But I have played all the all the final fantasies all like the
You know like I'm red dead redemption. I played Grand Theft Auto's I play a lot of video games
I have like over a thousand on my team
So like have you played any of the resident evil?
Resident evil yeah, I played resident evil village and and I play it's like another one really good with a cannibal family
Are you any good at it?
Yeah, I was actually like I got pretty far in the the village
It's just like it got too hard at one point and it's like we're just too too complicated like to find like but I was usually able to
Do pretty good enough. I'm good. Yeah, I love it
I want to like, you know, you can like play in VR you can like box and stuff like
What about the original resident evil to like the second resident evil with the original
I used to play that in high school like with like my friends like I would go like you know their house for like
I mean it's been the night and like I've been with other people until like five in the morning, so
Yeah
That was fun. That was a good days
Now now everyone's just on tiktok, you know, it's like when we show you a video of me playing the drums. Yeah
You can send it to you. Yeah, you can send it to my email
It's like how do I send it to you see the email my email address back there?
What do I do with it? You just you just sent write me an email, and then you write
You you attach the video the view clip to it
You're talking to chat chat GPT
It's like did you get it you send it already it's pretty fast one
Let's see, I need to go to my, okay, no, okay.
Okay, I don't see the gender to that email address.
Are you there, Mason?
Mason, Mason, are you there?
I like dick would you ever say that well because I'd seem like why should we go suck your dick you wanted to
Yeah, you want to suck a dick not us. That's my fucking brother. I don't need to suck his dick
You're the one on his fucking nuts and his ass wipe
I'm pretty much done like
Yeah. What was your plan? I heard summer up here and yeah, I'm gonna come up here and fucking because it wasn't certain.
The reason I even joined last night was because I saw what was being done to summer.
It wasn't fucking fair. And it also hurt me because I was like, what the fuck?
Yeah, yeah. You know, because you didn't want to hear what we have to say and you act like a baby.
You're just like, oh, I don't want to hear it. I don't want to hear it. I want this. I want that.
You throw tantrums and it's like, you need this. You want to see you're turning your back just like a baby.
this is like you're 45 years old you're a glorious fucking man dude like what's
the fuck stop acting like a bitch we got fucking mumbler in the slow one here
you know the left and right corner this is about again this is about
He's up there because he knows that I can fix it and he knows that I
He calls it that's who caused it
I don't I mean, I don't really know I wasn't there like from the beginning but I hold psyche responsible because he needs to be able to
You know manage and control everything and respect everybody. I did ask him yesterday
Would you have like booted on Alex NYPD?
If it wasn't for the $50 that Tracy provided he said no so to me that tells me he wanted Alex here
He wanted him despite him threatening his channel despite of all of that. He loves that shit
He loves it. Yeah, it's like psyche. This is not a joke
If you want to talk get up and have a little bit of respect for me in summer because you would do that
Am I right now? You'd be popping up going
Or pit what's the other girl that he's always fucking talking about none of these people even fuck with him
That's the fucking thing about it. Easy. Stay out of your mumblemouth douchebag. Let these three come here
You can understand every word I say
No, no, you sound like you're gonna cock in your mouth and
Can we get back to the main issue here with these three the important to you
Yeah, I would give you the cherry issue of how your parents didn't give you enough tension when you use the fucking child
That's what it is. Are you the guy that just said something about being over here?
You know what I'm saying?
Listen, I'm not scared of anybody. All right. I just want to know what is it that you keep putting the input to?
I want to hear what psyche has to say did I say I want to hear black RG has to say I said
I want to hear what psyche has to say or my fucking fear of anybody
We were in the middle of
And ghost and summer the ones that had the issue can everybody please just mute up and let us talk ghost is here
Since he is the person this is all about can we he fucking talk?
Hey ghost
Hello, that was really aggressive, but hello
So as I told you all that is not Tony's voice not even close
I'm not doing this fight
No, you're not because it's not your fight. I
Would like an apology. You should show sorry. I already apologized to you. I
apologize
You didn't apologize to him. I didn't
I did I apologize early in your channel I was also on your panel earlier if you're talking about today. I was on your panel
Everyone just put everyone just pile up on me
I don't know if it's like, um, you have, you know, alcohol that came out or that's how you really feel, but you said it in an after work
Relation tactics when you say everyone hate me don't do that
Don't
They don't feed him when he says everybody hates me let him sit in that shit because obviously we're fucking here cuz we don't hate you
Duh, that's why we're here
That isn't a hundred people much that
Wow
There you go putting a chat above your friends again psyche
You know having some class and you know
A pilot to your fucking channel is something out of psyche. All right. And remember the only reason you're having it because you wanted this kind of fucking bullshit
Fuck shit, not like peace and fucking tarot card readings. And this and that. This is what you want it.
Didn't see anything in my email. Are you sure you sent it there?
Yes, him your email again like that. I think I sent it to it, but I don't know what happened
Okay, it's in the back chat
Can you show me? Yeah
Go to the back chat was this private chat
It's like I don't see it man. I just posted it just now
Again
You see it now?
Sight!
You see it?
Sight, did you see what I told you now?
Hold on, Rando's here, hold on a second.
I need to let Rando on.
And oh, I can't let you on because you're not hold on. Oh, yeah, there you go
Are you live? Yes?
I'm here with me. Hey, how you doing man? Listen, I know everyone's cooking here
I don't want to be selfish and self-centered, but I made another song for the show. It's not AI
Go ahead
My job. Yeah, can I will you give me the honor insulting?
No, no, no, no, it's not can I play it dude? Come on
It took like ten minutes, okay, it's gonna take ten minutes. I know no it took me ten minutes to make this
I hope the audio goes through here we go
That's why I'm such a hero with no money in her bag
I can't even find the head the fuck me in my ass
What else will it say?
did you like it no I mean it's okay it's like it's okay I like the I like the
music but I didn't like the lyrics at all did you hear the lyrics did they go
through did they come through the sound waves because I'm next to master the
song I didn't give you the mp3
I
Serviced on to me here. All right. I got a good bye. Did you get it? Yeah?
What do you see?
You want to see hold on? Yeah
Well, you send me a YouTube video hold on wait
I'll show you the picture you sent me
What do you see site? Oh first I saw some pictures like of you and like I saw a video you're like in a store playing the drums
Let me see this one. Yeah, here
Very nice video
This you
Sorry, can you play it site? Yeah, hold on
Where's the video me in the store on the store, okay? Yeah, I don't know if that's a video though
Show me the one where you talking about in the store, okay
Right here
The one in the store is you're in a shoe store or something or not the drum store
There
Oh my god, my meals
Can you play it site? Can you play the video?
Pictures these are photographs, but then the next one is like where you have you're talking
So I didn't say anything
Why don't you say anything and then this one's blank and then this one is
Blank it's like oh, it's a YouTube link. Hold on
I don't know, I need to request access as a viewer.
I'm just gonna, okay, I think your request,
I don't know, it's in Google Drive or something like that,
so I can't get to it immediately.
Thank you, that's pretty cool though.
Where'd Rando go, Rando left, okay.
Hey, do you wanna hear a good song?
Mesa?
Want to hear a song guys
When you're a song guys
I'm gonna chat saying yes, there you go
This is I'm gonna leave after this one. So Mason. I'll see you later
My soul in a way, I shouldn't have thought out
A part of my brain was fried
I thought that I could win, but the chat just sighed
Won't you banish me?
They said I wasn't reasonable, nothing was debated
I am still me
You say you want
Don't care if it's soft day to hard our time you say it you gone don't play confused this ain't that show
We don't make those moves. No slander. Yeah, I said what I said you toss more fake dirt than a reddit thread
WWE got nothing on this chat false accusations man cut
Dumb things why's your avatar somebody's face real names real pics this ain't your place
Posting addresses like it's Halloween. You better send pizza with that scheme. No nudity. We beg and plead all Dean
No one wants your balls on screen flirty diamond stop the solo act those melted kisses ain't bringing sexy back
Dumb
It ain't that
and time began.